While and during these have again very similar meanings.
while 和 during 这些又具有非常相似的含义。
One thing is happening and another thing is happening at the same time.
一件事正在发生，另一件事正在同时发生。
The thing is happening at the same time.
事情同时发生。
But there are some differences in the way that they're used.
但是它们的使用方式存在一些差异。
So while is often used when we're talking about two actions action one eating action to watching a movie.
所以当我们谈论两个动作一个吃动作看电影时，经常使用while。
OK so that's the second action I usually eat something while watching a movie or watching movies a movie.
好的，这是我通常在看电影或看电影时吃东西的第二个动作。
Movies TV shows whatever.
电影电视节目什么的。
OK so there's an action going on there.
好的，那里有一个动作。
And usually while is used when we want to talk about two actions happening at the same time two simultaneous
当我们想谈论两个同时发生的两个动作时，通常使用 while
actions simultaneous is a very useful word.
同时行动是一个非常有用的词。
It means two things happening at the same time.
这意味着同时发生两件事。
I can also say simultaneously they were eating simultaneously.
我也可以同时说他们同时吃饭。
It is a little bit formal though to be honest with you now for during during is a little different and
虽然现在对你说实话有点正式，因为在此期间有点不同，而且
it's usually used for things that happen at the same time as a thing instead of another action.
它通常用于与一件事同时发生的事情，而不是另一个动作。
So for while you have usually two actions happening at the same time two things going on whereas during
因此，虽然您通常会同时发生两个动作，但同时发生两件事，而在此期间
is for a thing like a movie like a war like a meeting.
是为了一部电影，一场战争，一场会议。
So it could say for example don't use your phone during the meeting don't use your phone during the
所以它可以说例如在会议期间不要使用你的手机在会议期间不要使用你的手机
meeting.
会议。
So it's a thing here.
所以这是一件事。
It's a thing here.
这是一件事。
We don't have to say two actions that happen.
我们不必说发生的两个动作。
A thing is going on a lot of people suffered during the war.
许多人在战争中遭受了苦难。
War is no fun right.
战争一点也不好玩。
A lot of people suffered during the war.
许多人在战争中受苦。
No fun but it's a thing it's a thing.
没有乐趣，但它是一件事它是一件事。
I fell asleep during the movie.
我在看电影的时候睡着了。
Ok this one's also a very common thing that people say just a couple more examples.
好的，这也是一个很常见的事情，人们只说几个例子。
One of these is a little bit different for a while so I just want to show you how wild can be used slightly
其中一个在一段时间内有点不同，所以我只想向您展示如何稍微使用 wild
differently.
不同。
You can have a seat while you wait.
你可以在等待的时候坐下来。
So that's two actions happening at the same time.
所以这是同时发生的两个动作。
I should study while I have time.
我应该趁我有时间学习。
OK.
好的。
So now that that's a little bit different.
所以现在这有点不同。
While I have time then the examples that we did earlier but it still works here.
虽然我有时间然后我们之前做的例子，但它仍然适用于这里。
So this is a common while I have time while you can.
所以这是很常见的，而我有时间，而你可以。
This is another common phrase that uses while.
这是另一个使用 while 的常用短语。
OK.
好的。
And during the 90s a lot of Internet companies died died.
而在90年代，很多互联网公司死了就死了。
You could also say they went under they went under.
你也可以说他们倒下了。
OK during that period of time the 90s the 90s is a noun it's a thing.
好吧，那段时间 90s 90s 是一个名词，它是一个东西。
The 1990s.
1990 年代。